(Tsumura) Masaki Igawa and Mayumi Igawa each had their memories altered.
I was living as a different person.
(Yuri) You are... my husband!
(Igawa) The person I love is Mayumi.
Yusuke!
Come back and stop it!
Please don't follow me any further
No, her real name is Nanami Ishino.
This is the murderer who killed my husband seven years ago.
Mayumi Igawa left town?
(Tada) I'm currently waiting to hear from the driver who picked me up.
Someone came, Mr. Sudo...
Does that mean he was watching you?
Why would you do that? Where are you going?
Maybe he was chasing Mayumi.
(Mayumi) ≪I was happy≫
《Welcome back》 《Welcome back》
(Mayumi) ≪This is my life...≫
♬〜
《Kya! 》
(Mayumi) ≪But it was different≫
≪Everything… the life that was created≫
《Let's live somewhere else together》
♬〜
(Mayumi) >
(Mayumi) ≪Regain my life≫
(sound of door closing)
♬〜
(Presiding judge) Main defendant Nanami Ishino
Punished with 10 years' imprisonment》
(Kumiko) 《Please give me the death penalty! 》
``I killed my precious son! 》
《Death penalty...》
♬〜
Where are you heading?
here we go…
But it doesn't seem like she's blindly searching for Nanami Ishino.
Looks like you have something in mind
Did you have any contact with those two?
No, not really... I feel like we're just neighbors.
but…
When I think about it, I feel like those two were always watching me.
(Mitsuru/Takako)《Hello》《Ah, hello》
《Welcome》 《Yes, I'm coming》
《Back from work? " "Yeah"
《Thank you for your hard work》
Maybe he was watching you two.
Did you know that the two of you are different people?
♬〜
(chime)
(Kumiko) Yes.
It has been a while
Why are you here...
(Mayumi) Oh, please wait.
Shouldn't you be in jail? Why are you coming out?
Please, let me meet Miu!
Go back! (Mayumi) Ah...
Ah... no!
Ah... (Mayumi) No... no...
you! help me! That woman!
Please wait! Please wait! (Hironobu) What happened!
Um... (Hironobu) Call the police!
(Mayumi) Wait, wait! Miu... Where is Miu?
Please let me meet Miu
That child isn't there
Huh? (Hironobu) Not here
Come back!
What do you mean?
It's natural, isn't it? Murder...
There's no way a woman who killed her son could raise a child!
♬〜
Where is that kid?
I'll go from the back yes
♬〜
It's a children's home.
Nanami Ishino has a daughter
What... here?
Maybe
No one in my family takes care of me...
If Nanami Ishino appears here, it means her memory has returned.
Then I can ask what happened.
♬〜
Ah... Huh?
Mayumi...
Ninomiya!
Did any women visit you today?
♬〜
Mr. Igawa
What are you doing in a place like this... stop... I don't like it...
Hey!
let's go! Wait...
♬〜
Mayumi?
(Mitsuru) Uh... ah!
There's a car parked there. Run!
You want to see your daughter! Ugh...!
Then run away now!
quickly!
let's go!
♬〜
Ride!
Get it out! yes!
♬〜
(Tada) Huh? Did you manage to escape? What are you doing!
Yeah, Ninomiya was there too?
I don't know. That's no excuse.
It would have been better if we had caught it together.
It's over, it's over, Barca!
(Rie) Did Nanami Ishino run away?
(Tada) No, (Rie) What kind of lie is this?
If you know what it is, don't ask!
Mr. Ninomiya too?
Ah, it looks like I've come to help you.
I still think of her as my wife... right?
Is it love?
(Reception) Welcome, this is Tsumura, who made the reservation.
(Reception) Please fill in here
For now, here today
Sorry
Can you tell me what happened, Nanami Ishino?
Your memory has returned, hasn't it?
Don't be afraid
Huh?
I…
I didn't kill him.
♬〜
When I got home that day, my husband was dead.
《I'll be home in a little while》
(Nanami)《Arrived》
《Yoisho》
"Are you okay? Miwa hehehehe let's go》
《Tatsuya? 》
《I have a lot of luggage, so please help me》
♬〜
《Miu, please wait a moment》
(Nanami)《Ah...》
♬〜
《Tatsuya? 》
《(Police car siren)》
♬〜
《It's Nanami Ishino》
《Can I talk to you? 》
《What is your relationship with your husband Tatsuya?
It seems like it went bankrupt a long time ago.
《The cause is Tatsuya-san’s affair》
《What is that? 》 (Detective)《The fights never stopped.
I heard from a neighbor》
``You hated him, didn't you? 》
"what do you mean? 》
《Your fingerprints were on the knife that became the murder weapon》
``You killed Tatsuya, didn't you? 》
``What are you talking about? 》
``I didn't kill you! 》
《Please let me meet my daughter, please let me meet Miu! 》
(Detective)《Sit down! " "I beg you"
(Detective)《Stop! 》 《Please stop! 》
``This is some kind of mistake, please stop! 》
``I didn't kill you! 》 (Detective) 《Noisy! 》
《Please let me meet Miu》
Like that...
No matter what I said, they wouldn't listen to me
(Mayumi) After losing Miu, I was as good as dead.
How did you get out?
Can't remember something?
Someone in the same room accused me of something I didn't understand.
For some reason I was relegated to solitary confinement.
♬〜
(Mayumi) That day, when I ate dinner, I suddenly felt sleepy...
《(Sound of door opening)》
"(footsteps)"
♬〜
(Mayumi) The last thing I saw was a long hallway.
Gray...
After that...
"(footsteps)"
《Welcome back》
"I'm home"
I was with you
♬〜
Who got you out of jail?
Was there anyone else besides the prison guard?
There was one woman I didn't know.
it is…
Maybe...
this person
♬〜
(Guard)《This is Nanami Ishino》
(Guard)《Please》
♬〜
(Guard)《Seno...Yes》
Who is it?
Mutsumi Kosaka, my old boss.
(Kousaka) Nanami Ishino seems to have regained her memory.
I think it would be good to know about the Persona Shift program.
I will report again.
♬〜
When did you get your memory back?
At first...
when petr died
《Kya! 》
Peter?
Ah, this is the sparrow I kept.
I started getting a headache
Memories from before started coming to mind
At that time I didn't know what it was
But I remembered everything...
when I heard you died
《Ugh... ah...》
《Ah...》
Was that an accident?
(Mayumi) A man named Tada who worked at the same place as you came to my house.
♬〜
《Masaki Igawa met with an accident》
《What? 》 (Tada)《From the mountain path
It looks like it fell down to the river below...
《What, where is your husband now? 》
``Are you okay? 》
《I don't know where I am.》
(Tada)《This was discovered downstream》
《Like that...》
《It's very unfortunate, but...》
♬〜
(Mayumi) I remembered everything there.
(Mayumi) The man in front of me is
It was the man I saw at the place where I was taken.
Mr. Tada?
♬〜
Why Tada-san...
That man tampered with the memories of both of you.
I guess he was involved.
I wanted to know what was happening to me
The only way to do that is to investigate this man.
I thought if I missed this, I wouldn't be able to do that...
Is that why you pretended to think Tada was Masaki Igawa?
That's all I could think of right away
There's a way to stop it
It was the worst though
《Ma-kun...》
《What? 》
"good…"
《I was worried when I heard that there was an accident》
《Really good》
《So-so... Yeah...》
《It seems like my memory is getting cloudy.》
《You mistake me for Masaki Igawa》
《Ah, no, is it dangerous to erase Masaki Igawa's memory?》
《(Sound of door opening)》
《When I erased my memory that far back.
I can't predict what will happen at all.
《I'll try my best here》
《(Sound of power on)》
(Tada)《Good morning》
《Good morning Ma-kun》 《It's a nice morning. It's such a nice morning.》
《As expected... kiss me?》
《Hehehehe》 (Tada)《As expected》
(Mayumi) It was really the worst.
《If you experience excessive shock or stress,
The lid of memory opens
It seems that the brain malfunctions.
(Earphones Rie) 《But that's how much of a shock it is.''
The fact that you are receiving it means that there was love for it.》
《Even though they are a created couple》
``What is the headquarters saying? 》
(Earphones Tada) 《Please keep an eye on me for a while.》
"It's really hard" (Earphones Rie) "Why?
Do you look a little happy?
(Earphones Tada)《No, he doesn't look happy》
Eh, then I'll always remember...
sorry
I had no choice but to pretend I forgot you
After Igawa returned
Your memory was manipulated again, right?
So Igawa forgot about her
What happened to you?
《It's dangerous to stay here》
《Let's live somewhere else together》
"let's go"
《Ah...》
《(Electric sound)》
《Wow》
(Tada)《I feel lonely》
《But now things are back to normal》
《(Electric sound)》
♬〜
"(footsteps)"
《(Sound of door opening)》
《Are you okay? " "yes"
(Tada)《Okay, I'll put it back》 (Researcher)《Yes》
My memory didn't disappear...
Did you see or hear anything on the way there?
♬〜
Some kind of logo?
Something?
♬〜
Can I take a look? (Mayumi) Yes
Sorry
(shutter sound)
♬〜
Neurobis Corporation...
Looks like a pharmaceutical manufacturer.
♬〜
I'll look into it
What about Ninomiya? Can't you remember anything from before you lived with her?
Oh no... I'm sorry...
Have you heard of Neurovise?
home
please
Please just check to see if Miu is okay.
Understood
I told you not to do anything.
I understand that you are concerned about Ninomiya, but
We still don't know what happened to him.
Maybe he did something wrong too.
That's...but
Nanami Ishino was found guilty.
Anyway, please leave it to me.
Worst case, your son may be in danger too.
please
♬〜
(Tsujimoto) Itadakimasu
(Staff) Welcome. Ramen and gyoza, please.
(Salesperson) Yes.
I told you I wouldn't cooperate with you anymore.
It's my soliloquy
Seven years ago, a woman named Nanami Ishino was arrested for murdering her husband.
It's hot and after a while
Nanami Ishino's memory has been rewritten
Released into Morinuma Next Town as a different person
(coughing)
Wait... what are you talking about?
My memory has been rewritten
That's not science fiction.
A man named Yusuke Ninomiya also had his memory manipulated.
I lived with Nanami Ishino as a different person for two years.
Sigh... That can't happen, right?
Muroya is probably like that too.
Huh? Ninomiya Ishino Muroya
The memory tampering of the three people is probably...
A drug maker called Neurovice is involved.
What is it? the story
I don't know about Mr. Ninomiya though.
Both Muroya and Nanami Ishino went to prison for murder.
How can you manipulate your memory?
Of course it's just neurovise
Probably not possible...
Mr. Kosaka is giving guidance.
Huh?
Who is Kosaka-san? Is there anyone else?
What do you mean?
The noodles are growing
♬〜
(chime)
(sound of door opening)
OK?
Ah, if you like this...
Ah, sorry, maybe my tastes have changed.
I love you, ok then.
Well then...
that…
Would you like to have a drink together?
I'm glad I got my memory back
Please stop that
Huh? honorific language
I still have memories of you
When I gave birth to Miu
I almost died, huh?
That somehow helped me...
I can no longer have children
That's why I couldn't have children
it's not your fault
Eh... why would you say that...
I thought Piotr was cute
(Mayumi)《It's the name Ma-kun gave me.
Don't you feel like Peter's face? 》
♬〜
I let the second Peter escape.
Yeah, I see.
That's weird, isn't it?
You are in most of my happy memories
Even though it's all a lie
(Mayumi) We decided on Peter's name together.
We watched movies together until morning...
Huh? But isn't Peter lying?
I don't really understand
♬〜
(smartphone operation sound)
head…
Does that mean I should just hit him? Hmm
Ah, sorry, it was too bright.
What were you looking at? yeah? A little research
Who are you going to hit? Huh?
Don't hit me Don't hit me
(sound of door opening)
Ah... Good morning Good morning
I was wondering if you had any underwear or something?
thank you
Ah, sorry about Mayumi.
ah…
Can we talk a little?
Ah yes
Ah, this...
I brought a photo
I thought I might remember something
Ah... this was before Kento was born.
I started making it because I wanted to show it to a wise person someday.
our old photos
Kento really liked it.
He's watching me closely.
This is a photo from when I went to Kinosaki.
Maybe we can go on a trip just the two of us.
I'm sure it won't be another 20 years.
♬〜
This is Kento's young man's first sports day.
Running for the first time
I was nervous, but...
Look at me running so hard
daddy is crying
Sigh… I see.
Don't you remember at all?
Ah... I'm sorry.
Sigh...
"When I hit my head, my memory returned"
It was written on the internet
Huh? Huh?
Ah, that's not what I meant... Is that what you mean?
What does it mean? No... Huh? Yes, I won't hit you
Ah... yes, haha, I won't hit you.
Ah, good. Ah, I was surprised, hahahaha.
Sigh... Ah, just...
If you remember me
I'll do anything
to you…
I don't know what's going on with Yusuke.
But... it doesn't matter
I thought we'd be together forever
The day you proposed
The day you said "Let's be together forever"
Hehe, I guess I was annoyed.
It's obvious
What are you saying now? That's it
Kento and the three...
Let's grow old happily together...
If someday a wise man becomes independent...
At that time...
Let's live together again
For a long time
If I could go back to that time again
I... I'll do anything
So please
come back
♬〜
Sigh...
Sorry for getting you involved.
(sniffing sound)
I don't even know what I'm getting myself into...
But... I'll try what I can.
that's why…
So please wait
After…
Don't trust anyone
What about Tsumura-san too?
When I first saw that person
For a moment, an old memory
It's fragmentary, but it's come back to life.
What kind of memory do you have?
That person...
♬〜
killing people
(Sound of door opening) Ah...
Sorry, I didn't mean to eavesdrop...
(sound of door closing)
Ah...
I bought this underwear.
If you like
thank you
I hope to see you child
how old are you? your child
I'm 6 years old
Well then...
together until 4 years old
yes
Don't worry, there's no more love...
to your husband
Especially...
I just have false memories
♬〜
But 2 years...
No, excuse me
♬〜
(typing sound)
♬(whistle)
You seemed fine.
♬〜
Thank you very much
♬(whistle)
(cell phone vibration sound)
hello
📱(Tsujimoto) Can we meet and talk?
♬〜
Ou
Did you understand anything? Sigh… Please give me a break.
this is?
These are all people that Kosaka-san was in charge of.
All of them were sentenced to life imprisonment for murder.
Everyone...
I wasn't there
Huh? All nine people here
disappeared from prison
(Tsujimoto) As Mr. Tsumura said, I thought it was impossible.
I searched for "criminal" and "memory tampering".
Then, 7-8 years ago, on an internet bulletin board,
There was a thread that got a little excited.
What kind of content is it?
It's a plan to rewrite criminals' memories and reintegrate them into society.
Ha, what? That was right around that time
It seems like movies that play with memory have become popular.
``If someone were to rewrite the criminal's memory and reintegrate him into society as a different person,''
You don't have to pay unnecessary taxes to criminals, and
You can also collect taxes, so you can kill two birds with one stone, right? ”
I wrote it down.
What? Then
There was a note that said, ``Actually, that plan is moving forward.''
It became a bit of a hot topic.
Such a stupid plan is impossible
I think so too.
What if that plan really existed?
Doesn't it all make sense?
Both Muroya and Nanami Ishino were changed into different people and exposed in that plan.
What about Ninomiya? Is Ninomiya among these?
There was no record of Yusuke Ninomiya causing an incident or being arrested.
Sigh… (Tsujimoto) The other seven people here too.
I'm sure he's somewhere right now.
as a different person
♬〜
(Worker) Hey, hurry up!
(Teranishi) Goodbye (children) Goodbye.
Goodbye (children) Goodbye
Be careful
(Female) Yes (Imafuji) This is something I have delivered to you.
Thank you, please sign
Yes, this is it
♬〜
to whom? Talk to Kosaka-san...
(car running sound)
📱(conflict sound)
♬〜
(Mayumi) What did you do?
(Tada) Your former subordinate has noticed.
About the PS program
(Kousaka) I thought something like this shouldn't happen.
(Mayumi) What did you do to me and Mr. Ninomiya?
Mayumi was taken away
I'm home
Let's go get your life back too